<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Black Jack</string>

    <string name="ruleContent">It is similar to traditional Black Jack Game Rules with following exceptions:\n
        No bet amount, No insurance, No double down, No splits, Single hand per shuffle,\n
        Maximum 4 hits (6 cards max) per player\n
        Only two players: You and Dealer and You always play first.</string>

    <string name="gamerDescription"> When \"HIT\" button is pressed, top card from deck is dealt to player.\n
        When \"STAND\" button is pressed, player\'s turn is over and the total value of the hand is calculated.\n
        -Card values of 2 to 10 are totaled by their face values\n
        -Face cards (Jack, Queen, King) are totaled by 10, Aces are either 1 or 11\n
        Two kind of totals are calculated: \"Soft Total\" and \"Hard Total\"\n
        -\"Soft Total\" when Ace has value of 1\n
        -\"Hard Total\" when first Ace has value of 11, all others are counted as 1\n
        The final or best total will be the highest value of either \"Hard\" or \"Soft\" total which ever is closest to but not larger than 21.</string>


    <string name="condition">Whoever got Black Jack (an Ace with either 10, Jack, Queen or King) win the game.\n
        Whoever has the higher best total win the game.\n
        Whoever has best total higher than 21 lose the game, and a \"BUSTED\" message will be displayed.\n
        If you and dealer has the same best total, then you are tied and nobody wins.</string>

    <string name="dealerDescription">No \"HIT\" nor \"STAND\" for dealer.\n
        Dealer revealed it\'s first card, then calculate the \"Soft\" and \"Hard\" totals.\n
        Dealer will continue to draw the card from deck only if following condition are met:\n
        1. The \"Soft Total\" is less than 18 or \"Hard Total\" is less than 17, and\n
        2. The number of cards that dealer has is less than 6, and\n
        3. The best total of dealer is less than your best total, and\n
        4. The best total is not more than 21.</string>

    <string name="doneWith">You have finished the instructions and are ready to play</string>
</resources>
